<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Dolphins Hall</title>
    <link>https://dolphinshall.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Dolphins Hall</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dolphinshall.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Sneak Peek at Community, Youth &amp; Sports Complex</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-08-18-sneak-peek/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-08-18-sneak-peek/</guid>
      <description>We thought you may all like a sneak peek at some of the images of a model based on the design of the new Community, Youth &amp;amp; Sports Complex which we&amp;rsquo;ve received from the architects recently as it certainly made us excited and gave us a boost following all the recent drama around the project!
While we still wait for the release of the S106 monies for the project, we&amp;rsquo;re continuing to take the project seriously and getting ready to start the build as soon as planning permission is received.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release of S106 Funds - We are Making Some Progress</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-08-03-some-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-08-03-some-progress/</guid>
      <description>We want to thank our District Councillors, Stephen Hirst, Nikki Ind and Richard Norris for organising a meeting today between representatives from the Dolphins Recreation Centre (DRC), Cotswold District Council (CDC) Planning, CDC Legal and Tetbury Town Council (the Mayor and the Town Clerk).
The purpose of the meeting was to examine some of the Town Council&amp;rsquo;s concerns over their individual liability and S106 compliance in respect of Project One of the DRC Redevelopment Project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release of S106 Funds Declined by TTC</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-07-27-s106-refused/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-07-27-s106-refused/</guid>
      <description>We had high hopes for today as today was the day when Tetbury Town Council were going to agree to the forwarding of the S106 funding to the Redevelopment Project following the recommendation from their own Finance &amp;amp; Scrutiny Committee to do just that.
We are very sad however that tonight Tetbury Town Council refused to release the S106 monies assigned to the new Dolphins Redevelopment Project and yet again, the possibility of new community facilities from Tetbury takes another step back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Good News and a little bit of Progress.</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-07-13-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-07-13-progress/</guid>
      <description>So this evening we have some more good news to share.
Tonight Tetbury Town Council planning committee took the opportunity to once again review the plans for the Redevelopment Project and voted unanimously to withdraw their objection and now support the project. This means all statutory bodies now support the project and we await final sign off from Cotswold District Council which is due by the end of the month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good News For The Rec</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-07-10-good-news-for-the-rec/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-07-10-good-news-for-the-rec/</guid>
      <description>Even in lockdown it has been a busy time for trustees as we not only continue work on the Redevelopment Project, but we look at other ways of delivering on our commitment to the people of Tetbury to make the facilities the best they can be.
After years of neglect, we started work last year on improving the upkeep and maintenance of the Recreation Ground. The eagle eyed among you will have noticed the work we started last week to improve the facilities enjoyed by everyone out on the Recreation Ground.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proposed Redevelopment Project Update</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-06-25-project-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-06-25-project-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Given another inaccurate public announcement in respect of the project by a relation to two True to Tetbury Councillors as part of their continued misinformation campaign on the project, we thought it would be appropriate to provide an update on the progress we have made since our planning application was submitted.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dolphins Recreation Centre AGM</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-06-23-agm2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-06-23-agm2020/</guid>
      <description>The Dolphins Hall Management Committee AGM would typically be held sometime between April and June. The public at the AGM would elect six resident trustees to serve until the next AGM, and the trustees present the accounts to those present.
At last years AGM there were nearly one hundred people. Current social distancing rules make holding a meeting of this size impractical. Also, traditional paper-based secret ballots are quite high contact events, which is far from desirable at this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 23rd June 2020</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2020-06-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2020-06-23/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update on Plot 8</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-06-22-update-on-plot8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-06-22-update-on-plot8/</guid>
      <description>Since our update in May, discussions around Plot 8 have continued with both the Charity Commission and Tetbury Town Council. The trust’s position remains, as it always has been, that as trustees we have to act in the best interest of the trust, and it’s charitable aims, while also being mindful, if a decision we take can be challenged, we need to be able to provide sufficient evidence to support the outcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 4th June 2020</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2020-06-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2020-06-04/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 26th May 2020</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2020-05-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2020-05-26/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tetbury Town Council Planning Committee</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-05-14-ttc-planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-05-14-ttc-planning/</guid>
      <description>Very sad that tonight Tetbury Town Council&amp;rsquo;s Planning Committee failed to support the Dolphins Hall Redevelopment Project and decided to object to our planning application. Delays to the planning put the project at risk due to time limits on certain funds.
Their concerns on which their objections were based were either factually inaccurate or over points that the trustees had discussed with the Cotswold District Council Planning Officer and Conservation Officers prior to submitting the planning application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plot 8</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-05-13-plot-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-05-13-plot-8/</guid>
      <description>At the 2019 AGM, a Tetbury resident raised a query in concerning Plot 8 on the Recreation Ground.
Plot 8 includes the area of the Rec (known by some as the ‘training ground’) for which Tetbury Town Council have applied for an extension of the burial ground at St. Saviour’s church and has long been the subject of much debate.
The query put to us was around the ownership of this plot of land as the planning application submitted by Tetbury Town Council indicated it was the owner of the land.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 14th April 2020</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2020-04-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2020-04-14/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Build Planning Application</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/newbuild/updates/update-2020-04-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/newbuild/updates/update-2020-04-04/</guid>
      <description>We are delighted to announce that yesterday evening, 3rd April 2020, the Dolphins Recreation Centre submitted the full planning application for the Redevelopment Project!
This marks the end of a challenging and detailed design and review process, spanning almost eighteen months, and which has involved five public consultation events and two online surveys. We’ve had plenty of feedback which we have incorporated into our thinking, so we are hopeful we have listened and got this right!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Build Planning Application</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-04-04-planning-permission/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-04-04-planning-permission/</guid>
      <description>Given the current unusual and uncertain world which we find ourselves living in, and one where positive news stories seem hard to come by, we are delighted to announce that yesterday evening, the Dolphins Recreation Centre submitted the full planning application for the Redevelopment Project!
For more information please see the full announcement
There have been many challenges to overcome to get to this point, and it is not an understatement to say the kind words and supportive conversations have been all we’ve had to keep us going at points, so our heartfelt thanks go out to the community of Tetbury.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid-19 Update - Hall Closed Until End of April</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-03-22-hall-closed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-03-22-hall-closed/</guid>
      <description>In light of the amended guidance from the government announced on the 20th March 2020 the trustees have now decided to close the Dolphins Hall until at least the end of April 2020. All bookings at this time will be cancelled and refunded.
The trustees will continue to monitor the government advice and review the closure again if things change.
The sad reality is the closure will probably need to go on beyond this original period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid-19 Update</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-03-19-covid-19-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2020-03-19-covid-19-update/</guid>
      <description>The trustees have decided that at this time the hall will remain open for bookings. We do not feel it is our place to tell the users of the building if they can or cannot hold their meetings and events. We think it is for each individual and organisation to take the responsibility for making a judgement on what is appropriate at this time. We strongly suggest that people follow the latest government advice and do need to remind people that anyone running or attending an event at the Dolphins Hall does so at their own risk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 17th March 2020</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2020-03-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2020-03-17/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 18th February 2020</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2020-02-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2020-02-18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 20th January 2020</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2020-01-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2020-01-20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting December 2019</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-12/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Please note there was no trustees meeting in December 2019&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Build Consultation Update</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/newbuild/updates/update-2019-12-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/newbuild/updates/update-2019-12-15/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dolphinshall.org/images/posts/Update-2019-12-15/NewDH2019-12.png&#34; alt=&#34;Proposed New Dolphins Hall Development&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today marked the latest in our public consultation events at the Dolphins Hall and provided as an opportunity to give an update on the Redevelopment Project.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Build Consultation Update</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2019-12-15-new-build-consultation-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2019-12-15-new-build-consultation-update/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to everyone who turned up the consultation on the December 15th. For those who missed it, here’s a video of the plans.
  To find out more see a Full Update</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Build Drop In Consultation - December 15th 10am to 2pm</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/newbuild/updates/update-2019-11-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/newbuild/updates/update-2019-11-21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We appreciate it has been a while since we provided everyone with an update on the progress of the Redevelopment Project so as we approach the end of the year, we felt it was an appropriate time to let you know what has been going on behind the scenes the past few months.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 19th November 2019</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-11-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-11-19/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 22nd October 2019</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-10-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-10-22/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Website and Booking System</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2019-09-30-new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2019-09-30-new-website/</guid>
      <description>So today we release an update to our website. This new site will allow us to provide more frequent information. Most importantly it now also incorporates and links to a new booking system. The new system will enable you to book the Dolphins Hall online and pay using your credit or debit card. The system has only just been configured so there may be a glitch here and there. If you try to book and something goes wrong, please do get in touch here and let us know and we will sort it out as quickly as we can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 24th September 2019</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-09-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-09-24/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 20th August 2019</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-08-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-08-20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 16th July 2019</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-07-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-07-16/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 25th June 2019</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-06-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-06-25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees for 2019/20</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2019-06-24-trustees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2019-06-24-trustees/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With the 2019 AGM now complete the Dolphins Recreation Trust now has a new management committee that will be in place until the 2020 AGM.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 18th June 2019</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-06-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-06-18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 4th June 2019</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-06-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-06-04/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This was a briefing to approve the agenda of the AGM.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins Hall AGM – 4th June, 7:30pm</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2019-05-12-agm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/post/2019-05-12-agm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Dolphins Hall AGM will be held on the 4th of June 2019 at 7:30 pm at the Dolphins Hall. The meeting will be used to present a report on the work of the trust between April 2018 and March 2019 and present the accounts from the same period.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 23rd April 2019</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-04-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-04-23/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 19th March 2019</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-03-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-03-19/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 7th March 2019</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-03-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-03-07/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>24th Feb 2019 – Drop-In Consultation Session about the Plans</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/newbuild/updates/update-2019-02-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/newbuild/updates/update-2019-02-24/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t forget Sunday 24th is our next consultation day. Drop in any time between 10:30am and 4:00pm and see the first draft of plans for a new hall. You will be able to make comments, ask questions and raise concerns.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 19th February 2019</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-02-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-02-19/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 8th January 2019</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-01-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2019-01-08/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6th January 2019 – Drop-In Consultation Session about the Plans</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/newbuild/updates/update-2019-01-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/newbuild/updates/update-2019-01-08/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our second Drop-In session will be at the Dolphins Hall on Sunday 6th January 2019 10:00-16:30.
Please come along, ask questions, and give us your views about the proposals and where we go next.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The New Dolphins Hall Update 4th December 2018</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/newbuild/updates/update-2018-12-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/newbuild/updates/update-2018-12-06/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We’ve been busy analysing the answers you provided in our recent survey to determine a plan for the redevelopment of the Dolphin’s Hall and we’re pleased to confirm we are now in a position where we can share our plan with you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 4th December 2018</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2018-12-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2018-12-04/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 20th November 2018</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2018-11-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2018-11-20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 7th November 2019</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2018-11-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2018-11-07/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 23rd October 2018</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2018-10-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2018-10-23/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 18th September 2018</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2018-09-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2018-09-18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 21st August 2018</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2018-08-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2018-08-21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 7th August 2018</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2018-08-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2018-08-07/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 31st July 2018</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2018-07-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2018-07-31/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 26th July 2018</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2018-07-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2018-07-26/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trustees Meeting Minutes 24th July 2018</title>
      <link>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2018-07-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dolphinshall.org/minutes/dh-minutes-2018-07-24/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The minutes from this meeting can be downloaded in PDF format.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>